Paul Brickwell

Director of IT Front-End Web Developer



🖄 Portland Metro Area



M hello@paulbrickwell.com

https://paulbrickwell.com

With over 13 years of experience managing IT systems, I have worked with on on-site servers and entirely cloud-based solutions. I am currently pursuing a career change into Front-End Web Development after spending the last 5 years working on various web projects part time. I have completed JavaScript and Vue.js bootcamps in addition to extensive and continues self-training.

Education -

JavaScript Bootcamp Scrimba - 2021

Vue Bootcamp Scrimba - 2021

BS, Graphic Design Full Sail University 2014 - 2017

Computer Science Classes University of Alaska, Anchorage 2010 - 2014

Experience -

Craig Taylor Equipment // 2016 - Current

Front-End Web Developer // 2017 – Current

- Developed and maintain company website built with NuxtJS using GraphQL and Vuex to load data from Contentful.
- Build various web projects, integrations, and applications such as customer feedback capture portals and post-sale NPS surveys with **Zapier** and **Twilio**.
- Built, designed, and maintain internal employee portal based on WordPress with custom plugins.

Director of IT // 2021 – Current

- Manage IT systems for roughly 100 employees at 6 locations and provide solutions for fully remote employees.
- Maintain firewalls, site-to-site VPNs, subnets, and other network design on **Ubiquiti Edge** and **UniFi** platforms.
- Configure, deploy, and maintain computers and devices on varying operating systems such as Windows 10, MacOS, and iOS.
- Designed, deployed, and maintain support ticketing system with integrations into **Trello**.
- Strategize deployment of IT infrastructure and policies.

System Administrator // 2016 – 2021

- Worked with developers to assist with integration into custom DMS.
- Maintained Windows Server with local and cloud Active **Directory** policies.
- Created and deployed custom Windows 10 images.
- Provided support to employees for all hardware and software issues.

Marketing Manager // 2017 – 2021

- Identified marketing objectives and designed strategy based on these needs.
- Managed marketing budget including utilizing vendor coop funds.
- Created all print, digital, and radio ads.
- Managed social media accounts and website content.

Experience continued -

Brickwell, Inc. // 2015 - 2016

Office Manager

- Maintained scheduling and specialized insurance for large projects.
- Managed bookkeeping and payroll with **QuickBooks**.
- Designed and built online store with **Shopify**.

Immediate Care, Inc. // 2009 - 2015

IT Lead

- Managed multi-city network with VPN connection.
- Managed Windows Servers with **Microsoft Exchange**, custom policies, and roaming profiles.
- Maintained **99.9% uptime** on all services and hardware.

Paul Brickwell

Director of IT, Web Developer

Portland Metro Area

907.903.3922

https://paulbrickwell.com

Skills -

IT Infrastructure Management IT Operations IT Strategy

HTML / CSS

JavaScript

Vue.js

React

•••••

•••••

Network Design